克莱恩镇长呈现  欢乐园游会
-一人一个  -谢谢
- One for each of you. - Thanks.
祝你们愉快
Have fun.
-给你  -好啊
- There you go. - Yeah!
令人精神振奋吧
Now, doesn't that just lift your spirits?
我们再为霍金斯高中军乐队鼓鼓掌吧
Let's give another big hand for the Hawkins High Marching Band!
希望大家今晚玩得愉快
I hope you're all having a good time tonight.
你们玩得愉快吗
Are you having a good time?
我听不见
I can't hear you!
你们玩得愉快吗
Are you having a good time?
我想告诉大家  我们不惜重金
I want you to know that we spared no expense
向大家呈现
to provide you with
钱能买到的最好的娱乐
the very best entertainment that money can buy!
手臂放在里面
Keep your arms inside.
爸爸这下别想跑了
Dad can't get out now.
你俩为什么喜欢折磨我
Why do you two enjoy torturing me?
-因为好玩啊  -是啊  爸爸  因为好玩
- Because it's fun. - Yeah, Dad, 'cause it's fun!
我们走咯
Oh, here we go.
天呐
Oh, boy.
我不再废话了
But enough of me blabbering.
谁想看看焰火
Who here wants to see some fireworks?
拜托  这样的热情怎么行
Come on, now, you can do better than that.
谁想看看焰火
Who here wants to see some fireworks?
克莱恩镇长  罗恩县园游会
我们怎么停了
Uh, why are we stopping?
我给吉姆塞了五块钱
Because I slipped Jimmy a five.
什么
You what?
拜托  这可是最棒的座位
Come on, these are the best seats in the house.
最棒的座位
The best seats in the house.
国庆节快乐
Happy Fourth of July!
-好看吧  -嗯
- That was pretty, wasn't it? - Yeah.
是啊
Yeah.
妈妈  树
Mom, the trees.
-怎么了  宝贝  -树在动
- What, baby? - The trees are moving.
你为什么看树啊  宝贝
Why are you looking at the trees, baby?
看焰火啊  看焰火
The fireworks. Look at the fireworks!
那个好大  是吧
That was a big one, wasn't it?
怪奇物语  第三季 第七集
第七章
咬伤
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     草草
他说他在建造什么
He said he was building something.
翻译     草草
还说都是为了我
That it was all for me.
翻译     草草
建造什么
Building something...
-是指失灵者吗  -肯定是
- Is he talking about the flayed? - He must be.
校对     小酸奶
所以他跟我们猜的一样  在组建大军
So, he's building an army, just like we thought.
是啊  但他不是为了扩散
Yeah, but he's not building this army to spread.
是为了抵抗十一
He's building it to stop Eleven.
时间轴     Jessie
去年  一一把他关在了门里
Last year, El closed the gate on him.
我猜这让他很生气
I have a feeling that really pissed him off.
后期     8T
非常生气
Like, royally.
吸灵魔现在知道
And the Mind Flayer now knows
她是唯一能阻止他的人
that she's the only thing that can stop him.
-但如果她被除掉了  -完蛋
- But if she's out of the way-- - Game over.
总监     小酸奶
他还说
He also said
他要杀了你们所有人
he was gonna kill all of you.
真好啊
Yeah, well, that's nice.
你们听到了吗
Do you guys hear that?
只是焰火
It's just the fireworks.
比利
Billy...
他跟你说这话时  他在这里  这个房间里
When he told you this, it was here, in this room?
他知道我们在哪了
He knows we're here.
天呐  慢点
Jesus, slow down!
是啊  这是印第安纳波利斯500英里大奖赛吗
Yeah, what is this, like, the Indy 500?
是300
It's the Indy 300.
-不  呆瓜  是500  -是300
- No, dingus, it's 500! - It's 300!
一百万好了
Let's say a million.
-他们怎么了  -我不知道
- What is wrong with them? - I don't know.
-达斯汀  小心  -该死
- Dustin, watch out! - Shit!
你们没事吧
You guys all right back there?
他们没事
They're fine.
快  我们得走了
Come on. We gotta go, now.
-快出来  -下来
- Come on! Get out! - Let's go!
-我们来了  -试试便知了
- We're coming! - Here goes nothin'.
真讨厌
This sucks.
-你就像在冲浪  -冲浪  是啊
- You look like you're surfing! - Surfing! Yeah!
-他们像是醉了  -他们怎么会醉了
- They seem drunk. - Why would they be drunk?
我有天赋  看啊
I'm a natural! Check it out!
翻车了
Wipeout!
-他在发烧  -你在发烧
- He's burning up. - You're burning up.
-别动  史蒂夫  -天呐  不
- One sec, one sec. Steve, Steve. - God, no.
他的瞳孔完全放大了
His pupils are super dilated.
或许他被下了药
Maybe he's drugged.
史蒂夫  你被下药了吗
Steve, are you drugged?
说几次啊  爸爸
How many times, Dad?
我不嗑药  我只吸大麻
I don't do drugs. It's only marijuana.
这可不好玩  我需要知道他们对你做了什么
This isn't funny, okay? I need to know what they did to you.
-你们会死吗  -波波
- Are you gonna die on us? - Boop.
我们都会死  小怪孩朋友
We all die, my strange little child friend.
重点是怎么死
It's just a matter of how...
什么时候死
and when.
上面的人会在找我们
They're gonna be looking for us up there,
我需要你告诉我  你把车停在了哪
so I need you to tell me where you parked your car.
我们可以去美食街停留一下吗
Oh, can we make a pit stop at the food court?
我太想吃热狗棒了
I would kill for a hot dog on a stick.
好  好  食物
All right. Yeah, food.
你想吃多少吃多少
Yes, you can have as much food as you want,
但你必须告诉我你把车停哪了
but only if you tell me where your car is parked.
车开不了了
The car's off the board.
-什么  -他们拿走了车钥匙
- What? - They took the keys.
苏联人  他们拿走了钥匙
The Russians, they took the keys.
好久之前了
Like, forever ago.
真糟糕  是吧
That's a bummer, right?
LYNX运输
天呐  味道太好了
Oh, my God, that tastes so good.
史蒂夫  你尝到空气的味道了吗
Steve, can you taste the air?
是啊  尝到了
I taste it! I taste it!
-站住  -该死  快跑
- Stop! - Shit! Come on! Come on!
快站住
Stop right there!
-好好好  -我们跑什么
- Okay, okay, okay! - Why are we running?
嗯  这样就行
Yeah. That's good like that.
远离窗户
Hey, get away from the windows.
靠近了
It's close.
它去哪了
Where'd it go?
我去
Holy shit.
一一
El!
拉啊
Pull!
南茜  开枪
Nancy, shoot it!
快  卢卡斯
Come on! Lucas!
拉
Pull!
一一  你没事吧
El! El, you okay?
-快走  -快走
- Go, go, go! - Come on, come on, go!
-快走  -快  快
- Go! - Hurry up! Come on!
大家快出去
Everybody out!
-快走  -快
- Go! - Go, come on!
走走走
Go, go, go, go!
-快走  -快
- Come on! - Come on!
快  快
Come on! Come on!
上去  快走
Get in. Right here.
开车  开车
Drive! Drive!
我们去哪
Where are we going?
相信我
Just trust me.
安全
All clear.
博士
Doc!
我怎么跟你说的
What did I tell you?!
时速88英里
Eighty-eight miles per hour!
来
Come on.
时间错位发生在1:20整
The temporal displacement occurred exactly 1:20...
-你俩  坐下  -不不  这座位太近了
- You two, sit. - No, no, no! These seats are too close!
-哥们  这座位太烂了  -那就别看电影
- Dude, these seats blow. - Then don't watch the movie.
-我们想看  -那就看啊
- We wanna watch it. - Then watch it!
抱歉
Sorry.
不管怎样
Whatever you do,
别去别的地方
don't... go... anywhere.
好吧  爸爸
Fine, Dad.
该问的问题是"他们在哪个时间"
The appropriate question is "When the hell are they?"
瞧  爱因斯坦刚成为
You see, Einstein has just become
-世界首个时间旅行者  -抱歉
- the world's first time traveler! - Sorry. Sorry.
我把他  送去了未来
I sent him... into the future!
好了  正式决定了
Okay, it's official.
我绝对不要孩子
I'm never having kids.
-我们来这里干什么  -躲藏
- What are we doing here? - We're laying low.
等风头过去
Cooling off.
就像奥斯瓦尔德[刺杀肯尼迪的凶手]
Like Oswald.
奥斯瓦尔德在影院里被抓到  还被打死了
Oswald was found in a theater and shot to death.
那是一周后了
A week later.
重点是  他的计划没成功
The point is, his plan didn't work.
那是因为是个陷阱
Only because it was a setup.
-什么  -他就是个替罪羊
- What? - He was just a patsy.
你开玩笑的吧
Tell me you're joking.
我们得离开这里
We need to get outta here.
好吧  你看着那俩傻蛋
All right, you watch Tweedledee and Tweedledum.
-别让他们乱跑  -你去哪
- Make sure they don't go anywhere. - Where are you going?
找辆车
To find us a ride.
小心
Look out!
博士
Doc...
-怎么回事  -我不知道
- What's happening? - I have no idea.
你是说你建了台时光机
Are you telling me that you built a time machine...
-他在说什么  -他在给我指关掉机器的
- What's he saying? - He's showing me the location of the key
钥匙的位置
to turn off the machine.
抱歉  有两把钥匙
Sorry, "Keys." Two keys.
两人规则
Two-man rule.
-什么  -对  两人  两把钥匙
- Two-man rule? - Yeah, two men, two keys, like a...
就像核武发射
nuclear launch.
但要拿到钥匙  需要进入地库
But, uh, to retrieve the keys, there is a vault.
要打开地库
And to open the vault,
需要输入普朗克常数
you need to enter Planck's constant.
-普朗克什么  -普朗克常数
- Planck's what? - Planck's constant.
-一个著名的数字  -好  那我们拿到钥匙
- It's a very famous number. - All right, so we get the keys,
然后关掉机器
and then we turn the machine off.
他就是这么说的
That's what he says.
好  应该不太难  我们可以的
All right, well, that shouldn't be too hard. We can do this.
乔伊  你听到他说那里就像
Joyce, did you hear the part where he said the place was like
固若金汤的城堡了吧
an impenetrable fortress?
是啊  但肯定也有进路的
Yeah, but there has to be a way in.
是啊  有  我们的军队
Yeah, there is. Our military.
-他们要来了  -我们不能确定
- Who are coming. - Well, we don't know that anymore
因为你吼了他们
because you yelled at them
就好像那是家长会似的
like it was a parent-teacher conference,
然后还挂了他们的电话
and then you hung up on them,
所以  我们不能确定现在的情况
so we don't know what the hell's going on,
因为我们  等等  我们在干什么...
because now we're-- Wait, wait, what are we do
等等  对了
Wait, that's right!
我们正要去营救我们的孩子
We're on our way to rescue our children
因为大坏国庆节庆典要害他们
from the big, bad Fourth of July celebration!
知道吗  如果你受不了  那就调头
You know what, if you can't handle this, then just turn around
先让我下车吧
and drop me off first.
你要做什么
What are you gonna do?
你要走回霍金斯吗
You gonna walk back to Hawkins?
只要能远离你  我干什么都行
I will do anything if it gets me away from you!
孩子们  孩子们
Children! Children! Children!
这无休无止的斗嘴起初还算有趣
This interminable bickering was amusing at first,
但越来越烦人了
but it's getting very stale
我们还要开很久的车呢
and we've still got a long drive ahead of us.
所以  你俩就少说屁话
So, why don't you two cut the horseshit
直接承认
and get to the part where
你们对彼此的性吸引吧
you admit your sexual feelings for one another?
你扯太远了
You are way off base, buddy!
少来了
Oh, spare me, spare me, spare me!
是的  他很野蛮  我知道
Yes, yes, he's a brute. I know.
大概让你回忆起了不好的旧爱
Probably reminds you of a bad relationship,
天呐  你很想找个好男人安顿下来
and, gosh, you'd really like a nice man to settle down with,
但承认吧
but, admit it,
你很想知道他在床上什么样
you're real curious to know what he's like in the sack.
还有你
And you.
你就是个大巨婴
Well, you're just a big manbaby
宁可逞强  也不愿袒露真心
who'd rather act tough than show his true feelings,
因为上次你敞开心扉时  你受了伤
because the last time you opened your heart, you got hurt.
现在  你们不愿承认你们的感情
And now, rather than admit these feelings,
而是跟彼此周旋
you're dancing around one another
上演着令人麻痹的笨拙交配仪式
with this mind-numbing and frankly boorish mating ritual.
拜托  为了我
So, please, for my sake,
你们要么别吵了  要么靠边停
either quit your bickering, or pull over,
脱掉衣服
tear off those clothes,
赶紧发泄完拉倒
and get it over with already!
你说什么了
What was that?
我说他们该做爱
I told them they should have sex.
他们还没做过爱吗
They have not had sex?
没有
No.
欢迎来到印第安纳州
布拉德利大块头
外用酒精
纱布
好  扶她坐下
Okay, get her down.
好
Okay.
我看看
Lemme see.
该死
Oh, shit.
你干什么
What-- What-- Hey, what are you doing?
清理伤口
I'm cleaning the wound.
不  首先得止血
No, first, we need to stop the bleeding,
然后清理  然后消毒  然后缠绷带
then clean, then disinfect, then bandage.
我滑滑板  相信我
I skateboard. Trust me.
迈克  摁住
Mike, hold this.
稳稳地压好
Keep the pressure on it, nice and firm, okay?
我们需要水  肥皂
We're gonna need water, soap.
-好的  -好
- Yeah, okay. - All right.
这些东西有用吗
Does any of this help?
没用
No.
去找条毛巾和碗来
Go get me a washcloth and a bowl.
-碗  -卢卡斯
- A bowl? - Lucas.
-快去  -好
- Go. - Okay.
你觉得那玩意像什么
What did that thing look like to you?
像医院的那个  但更大了
Like that thing in the hospital, only bigger.
是啊  大多了
Yeah, a lot bigger.
汤姆和布鲁斯  他们合并成了一个  是吧
Like, Tom and Bruce, they merged to become one, right?
德里斯科尔一直说
And-- And Driscoll kept saying
她得回到源头去
how she needed to go back to the source--
等等  你觉得那里面有德里斯科尔吗
Wait, you think Driscoll's in there?
可能吧
Maybe.
可能还有海瑟  珍妮特
And-- And-- And maybe Heather and Janet, too,
天知道还有谁
and God knows who else.
我不知道我们要怎么杀了那玩意  但如果杀了他
I don't know how we're gonna kill this thing, but if we do--
-失灵者也都会死  -我们能了结此事
- We kill all the flayed. - And... we end this.
或许吧
Maybe.
我只知道
All I know is...
我们需要一一
we need El.
碗
Bowl...
-怎么会在燕麦片区  -我不知道
- Why wouldn't it be with the cereal? - I don't know.
你还用碗做什么
What else do you use a bowl for?
我不知道
I-- I don't know.
该死
Oh, shit.
撒旦之子
Satan's Baby.
烟花
你发射过这玩意吗
You ever shot one of these suckers?
没有  厉害吗
No. Is it sweet?
-可不止呢  -那可不像碗
- That's an understatement. - That doesn't look like a bowl.
不  这好多了
Nah, it's way better.
这玩意标注"18岁以上"是有原因的
There is a reason this warning label says "18 or older."
这玩意有150克黑火药
This sucker is filled with 150 grains of black powder.
也就是火药
AKA gunpowder.
把俩绑在一起  比M80还厉害
Strap two of these together, and it's bigger than an M-80.
五个
Five of them,
就赶得上炸药了
we've got ourselves a stick of dynamite.
你想拿烟花杀了那玩意
You wanna kill that thing with fireworks?
你有更好的主意吗
Do you have a better idea?
有  十一
Uh, yeah. Eleven.
对付那玩意吗  她会需要支援的
Against that thing? She's gonna need some backup.
天呐
Oh, my God.
拿着
Hold this.
疼吗
Does that hurt?
还行
Uh, not bad.
你会留个很酷的疤
You're gonna have an awesome scar.
你看上去会更厉害
You'll look even more badass.
贱样
Bitchin'.
对  贱样
Yeah, bitchin'.
一一
El...
怎么
Yeah?
我有话想对你说
I've been meaning to tell you something.
分手
It's just, being broken up,
让我好难受
it's been hard.
我...
And...
很高兴你和麦克斯成了朋友
I like that you and Max are friends now.
但起初  我嫉妒了  生气了
It's just, I was jealous at first, and-- and angry.
所以我才说了那些蠢话
And that's why I said all that stupid stuff.
我希望独占你
And it's like I wanted you all to myself.
现在我意识到  这是不公平的
And now I realize how unfair that is.
自私的  我...很抱歉
And selfish. And, like... I'm sorry.
我从未有过这样的感觉
I just, like, I've never felt like this,
对任何人都没有
you know, with anyone before...
所以
and...
人说这让你疯狂
You know, they do say it makes you crazy.
什么让你疯狂
What makes you crazy?
你没听过那句话吗
You never-- You never heard that term...
就是那个说法
You know, like the phrase, like...
"...让你疯狂"  就是那个词
"Blank makes you crazy," Like the word...
"女友"吗  -不不不  不是女友
- "Girlfriends"? - No, no, no, no, not-- not girlfriends.
-"男友"  -不不不  不是男友
- "Boyfriends." - No! No, no, not boyfriends either.
-是...一种感觉  -感觉
- It's like-- It's like a feeling or... - A feeling...
对  就像...
Yeah, like something... Like,
老人有时会对彼此说那个
old people say it to each other sometimes.
-老人  -对
- Old people? - Yeah.
我想说的是
What I wanna say is...
我...
that I just...
我知道我...
I know that I--
重复  红色警报
I repeat... this is a code red!
达斯汀
Dustin?
迈克
Mike?
-达斯汀  -迈克
- Dustin! - Mike!
天呐  听好了  我知道我玩失踪了
Oh, my God, you have to listen. I know I've been MIA,
抱歉  不是因为我生气了
and I'm sorry, it's not because I'm mad.
我是生气了
I mean, I actually was mad,
但也是因为  我被困在了地下
but it's also because I was trapped underground
在一个秘密苏联基地里
in a secret Russian base.
达斯汀  你说太快了  我听不懂
Dustin, you're going way too fast. I can't understand you.
我知道听上去很疯狂
I know that sounds insane,
但苏联人渗透进了霍金斯
but the Russians have infiltrated Hawkins!
苏联人啊
The goddamn Russians!
他们还用...开启入口
And now-- they're using-- to open the gate.
达斯汀  你信号不好
Dustin, you're-- you're breaking up.
他们在追杀我们  我们没有出路
And now they're after us and we don't have a way out of here,
我需要你们来救我们  南茜能开车吗
so I need you to come and get us. Can Nancy drive?
达斯汀  你信号不好
Dustin, you're cutting out.
-迈克  -达斯汀  你在吗
- Mike? - Dustin, you there?
迈克  你收到吗
Mike? Mike, do you copy?
达斯汀
Dustin--
该死  别现在啊  别啊  迈克
Shit! Not now. Please, not now. Mike!
-达斯汀  -迈克
- Dustin! - Mike!
怎么了
What is it?
你有电池吗  双A的
Do you have any batteries? Double-A?
我怎么会有电池
Why would I have batteries?
我总随身带电池
I always carry batteries.
那有什么问题
Then what's the problem?
我需要八个
I need eight.
八个
Eight?
该死  我们得启用B计划了
Shit. Guess we'll have to go to plan B.
B计划  那是什么
Plan B? What's plan B?
他们人呢
Where... are they?
太棒了
That's amazing.
我刚刚并没有
So, like, I wasn't totally focused
非常全神贯注  但是
in there or anything, but...
我确定
I'm pretty sure...
那妈想上她儿子
that mom was trying to bang her son.
等等  那个性感小妞是艾利克斯·基顿他妈吗
Wait, wait, the hot chick was Alex P. Keaton's mom?
是啊  我确定是的
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
但他们同龄啊
But they're the same age.
不  他穿越时间了
No, but he went back in time.
那为什么要叫《回到未来》
Then why is it called Back to the Future?
他得回未来去
He has to go back to the future
因为他在未来
because he's in the past.
所以未来就是现在
So, the future is actually the present,
他的时代
which is his time.
什么
Wh... What?
不  该我了  你喝够多了
No, no, it's my turn. You've had enough.
罗宾
Hey, Robin.
你会想看看的
You gotta check this out.
看啊
Check this...
天花板  好美啊
This... The ceiling, it's beautiful.
待在这里  跟司木露过一遍计划
Stay here, go over the plans with Smirnoff.
-我能帮忙找  -不  你会吓到孩子
- I can help look. - No, you'll scare the children.
吉姆  如果是为了之前的事
Jim, if this is about earlier--
别走开  弗洛伊德
Stay put, Freud!
听到了吗  别动
You hear me? Stay put!
不管你怎么说克莱恩
You know, say what you will about Kline,
他可真会开派对
he certainly knows how to throw a party.
我替他道歉了
I'm sorry about him, by the way.
-谁  拉里吗  -不  莫里
- Who, Larry? - No, Murray.
他就是个变态  喜欢惹人生气
He's a sick individual who likes to get under people's skin.
别让他惹我们生气
So, let's not let him, you know, get under our skin.
我没有
I'm not, I haven't.
你似乎比往常更安静了
I just, you seem a little more quiet than usual.
-我只想找的孩子们  -好
- I just-- I just wanna find the kids. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我努力一试
I'll give it my best shot.
你赢了只熊
You won yourself a bear!
谢谢  给你
Thank you. Here you go.
克莱恩镇长  再来一张
Mayor Kline! One more, one more.
好好笑  好的
Big smile. There we go.
-小心  -国庆节快乐  混蛋
- Watch it! - Happy Fourth, dick.
快快快
Come on, come on, come on!
接听啊  你们这群共党混蛋
Pick up, pick up, pick up, you commie bastards!
布拉德利大块头
-安静  -抱歉
- Quiet. - Oh, sorry.
-你怎么能喝那个  -因为好喝
- How do you even drink that? - Because it's delicious.
什么
What?
就像卡朋特的《怪形》
It's like Carpenter's The Thing.
原版是经典
The original is a classic,
毫无疑问
no question about it.
但翻拍
But the remake...
更甜  更大胆
Sweeter, bolder...
更好喝
better.
你疯了
You're insane.
那你更喜欢原版《怪形》吗
So, you prefer the original Thing?
什么  不  我不是说《怪形》
What? No, I'm not talking about The Thing,
我是说新可乐
I'm talking about New Coke.
概念是一样的  哥们
It's the same concept, dude.
其实  才不是呢
Uh, actually, it's not the same concept.
就是的
It is the same concept.
-不是的  -是的
- No, it's not. - Yes, it is.
抱歉
Sorry.
你找到他了吗
Did you... find him?
电影院
The movies?
达斯汀被入口的事吓坏了
Dustin's so freaked out about the gate,
于是决定去看电影吗
he decides to go watch a movie?
是啊  非常合理
Yeah, makes total sense.
你确定他说的是"入口"不是"好"吗
You're positive he said "gate" and not "great"?
是啊  比如"我看的电影好棒"
Yeah, like, "This movie I'm watching is great."
听上去像"入口"
Sounded like "gate."
那就怪不得吸灵魔还活着了
Which would explain how the Mind Flayer's still alive.
是啊  我们只需要再关上入口一次
Yeah, we just have to shut it again.
然后怪物就死了
Then the monster dies.
如果不行  我们还有卢卡斯的烟花
But if not, we always have Lucas' fireworks.
继续嘲讽我的计划吧  麦克斯
Keep mocking my plan, Max. Keep mocking it.
我想再听你说一次  因为你总质疑我
I wanna hear you say it again, because you keep doubting me.
你总质疑我
You keep doubting me!
-荒唐  -威尔
- Ridiculous. - Will?
我们能证明他们错了  是吧
We're gonna prove 'em wrong, right?
天花板不转了
The ceiling stopped spinning for me.
你呢
Is it still spinning for you?
我去
Holy shit.
不转了
No.
你觉得我们都吐出去了吗
You think we puked it all up?
可能吧  问我点什么
Maybe. Ask me something.
审讯我
Interrogate me.
好  审讯你  好啊
Okay. Interrogate you. Sure.
你最后一次尿裤子是什么时候
When was the last time you, uh, peed your pants?
今天
Today.
什么
What?
苏联医生掏出骨锯的时候
When the Russian doctor took out the bone saw.
天呐
Oh, my God.
就尿了一点点
It was just a little bit, though.
是啊  她还没排净呢
Yeah, it's definitely still in her system.
-好了  换我  -好
- All right, my turn. - Okay.
说吧
Hit me.
你...
Have you...
爱过什么人吗
ever been in love?
爱过  南茜·维勒
Yep. Nancy Wheeler.
高四第一学期
First semester, senior year.
天呐
Oh, my God.
她好娇气啊
She's such a priss.
其实  并不
Turns out, not really.
你还爱着南茜吗
Are you still in love with Nancy?
-没有  -为什么
- No. - Why not?
可能是因为我找到了
I think it's because I found
更合适我的人
someone who's a little bit better for me.
好疯狂
It's crazy.
自从达斯汀回来  他一直在说
Ever since Dustin got home, he's been saying,
"你得找到自己的苏茜"
"You know, you gotta find your Suzie. You gotta find your Suzie."
等等  苏茜是谁
Wait, who's Suzie?
夏令营的姑娘  好像是他女友
It's some girl from camp, I guess his girlfriend.
老实说  我不确定她是真实存在的
To be honest with you, I'm not 100% sure she's even real.
但那不是重点
But that's not-- that's not really the point.
不重要  重要的是
That doesn't matter. The point is,
我喜欢的那个女孩
this girl, you know, the one that I like,
她是我上学时从未注意过的人
it's somebody that I... didn't even talk to in school.
真不知为什么
And I don't even know why.
或许是担心被汤米·H嘲笑
Maybe 'cause Tommy H. would've made fun of me or...
或是担心我当不上
I wouldn't be...
舞会国王
prom king.
真蠢  达斯汀是对的
It's stupid. I mean, Dustin's right,
那全都是扯淡的
it's all just a bunch of bullshit anyways.
因为  想起来
Because, when I think about it,
我就该一直跟她玩的
I should've been hanging out with this girl the whole time.
首先  她很风趣幽默
First of all, she's hilarious. She's so funny.
这个夏天  我好久
I feel like, this summer, I have laughed harder
都没笑得
than I have laughed...
那么开心了
in a really long time.
她还聪明
And she's smart.
比我聪明多了
Way smarter than me.
她能破解绝密苏联密文
You know, she can crack, like, top secret Russian codes and...
她显然不像我认识的任何人
You know? She's honestly unlike anyone I've ever even met before.
罗宾
Robin?
罗宾  你是服药过量了吗
Robin, did you just OD in there?
没有
No.
我
I...
还活着
am still alive.
地板好恶心
The floor's disgusting.
是啊  我衣服上反正
Yeah, well, I already got
也都是血和呕吐物了
a bunch of blood and puke on my shirt, so...
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
什么
About?
这个女孩
This girl.
她听上去很棒
She sounds awesome.
她是很棒  那男人呢
She is awesome. And what about the guy?
我觉得他嗑药了  脑筋不清醒
I think he's on drugs, and he's not thinking straight.
是吗  我可觉得
Really? 'Cause I think
他脑子比平常清醒多了
he's thinking a lot more clearly than usual.
不是的
He's not.
听着
Look...
他根本不了解这个姑娘
he doesn't even know this girl.
如果他真了解她
And if he did know her,
真的了解她
like-- like really know her,
我觉得他都不会想跟她做朋友
I don't think he'd even want to be her friend.
不  不是的  这是不可能的
No, that's not true. No way is that true.
听我说  史蒂夫
Listen to me, Steve.
虽然让我很震惊
It's shocked me to my core,
但我喜欢你
but I like you.
我真的很喜欢你
I really like you.
但我不像你的其他朋友
But I'm not like your other friends.
我也不像南茜·维勒
And I'm not like Nancy Wheeler.
罗宾  所以我才喜欢你
Robin, that's exactly why I like you.
你记得我说的  滴答老师的课吗
Do you remember what I said about Click's class?
关于我的嫉妒  执迷
About me being jealous and, like, obsessed?
嗯
Yeah.
不是因为我喜欢你
It isn't because I had a crush on you.
是因为
It's because...
她总盯着你看
she wouldn't stop staring at you.
滴答老师吗
Mrs. Click?
塔米·汤普森
Tammy Thompson.
我希望她看我
I wanted her to look at me.
但她的眼睛就是死死盯着你
But... she couldn't pull her eyes away from you
和你讨厌的头发
and your stupid hair.
我不能理解  因为你总把百吉饼碎屑
And I didn't understand, because you would get
撒一地
bagel crumbs all over the floor.
你还提愚蠢的问题
And you asked dumb questions.
你还是个混蛋
And you were a douchebag.
你都不喜欢她
And-- And you didn't even like her and...
我会回到家
I would go home...
冲我的枕头里吼
and just scream into my pillow.
但塔米·汤普森是个女孩
But Tammy Thompson's a girl.
史蒂夫
Steve.
怎么
Yeah?
我去
Holy shit.
是啊
Yeah.
我去
Holy shit.
史蒂夫
Steve...
你是服药过量了吗
did you OD over there?
不  我就是
No, I just, uh...
在想
just thinking.
好吧
Okay.
是啊
I mean, yeah.
塔米·汤普森  她是挺可爱
Tammy Thompson, you know, she's cute and all, but...
但是
I mean,
她好没用
she's a total dud.
才不是呢
She is not.
就是  她想做个歌手
Yes, she is. She wants to be, like, a singer.
还想搬去纳什维尔
She wants to move to, like, Nashville and shit.
-她有梦想  -她唱歌跑调
- She has dreams. - She can't even hold a tune.
她基本上是音痴  你听过她唱歌吗
She's practically tone-deaf. Have you heard her?
总是跑调
All the time.
*你今晚看到我*
*You see me now tonight*
-闭嘴  -*你看到...*
- Shut up. - *You see me...*
-她唱歌才不是那样呢  -就是的
- She does not sound like that. - She sounds exactly--
-我模仿得可像了  -她才不呢
- That's a great impersonation of her. - She does not.
你听上去像布偶
You sound like a Muppet.
是她像
She sounds like a Muppet.
她像生孩子的布偶
She sounds like a Muppet giving birth.
*如果你可以紧紧抱住我*
*And if you could hold me tight*
*我们会永不放手*
*We'll be holding on forever*
-是吧  -说得对
- Exactly. - I know!
好了
Okay.
搞什么
What the hell?
这是干什么
And why all this?
如果我关闭钥匙  就像关闭一辆车
If I just turn the keys, it's like turning off a car.
但车还是好用的  是吧
But then the car still works, does it not?
对
Yes.
你是希望车
And do you want the car
还能用呢  还是希望它爆炸
to still work or do you want it to explode?
我希望车爆炸
I want the car to explode.
很好  那就这样办
Good. Then do this.
只需要确保
Just make sure you are
车炸的时候你不在附近  场面会很可怕
nowhere near it when it does. It is not pretty.
人会被烧成渣
Turns people into dust.
然后
And then...
就结束了
It's over.
我可以成为美国人  也这样享受欢乐  是吧
And I become an American citizen and join in the fun, yes?
谁说你得是美国人才能享受欢乐的
Who said you had to be an American to join the fun?
没有比这更美国的了  朋友
It doesn't get more American than this, my friend.
肥胖食物  丑陋的堕落
Fatty foods, ugly decadence,
被操纵的游戏
rigged games...
50张票  谢谢
Fifteen tickets, please.
-游戏都是被操纵的吗  -对
- They are rigged, these games? - Yes.
看上去不像啊
They do not look rigged.
就是这样  亲爱的阿列克西
That's just it, my dear Alexei.
他们被设计成有公平的幻象
They have been designed to present the illusion of fairness!
但都是骗人的把戏
But it's all a scam, a trick,
为了让你掏钱给有钱人
to put your money in the rich man's pocket.
这  我亲爱的朋友
That, my dear friend, is...
就是美国
America.
但是
But, hey...
请便吧
knock yourself out.
你去哪
Where are you going?
去给咱俩找最接近食物的东西
To get us the closest thing to food I can find.
凯伦
Karen.
上来吧
Step right up!
感受风推动着你
...feel the wind push you back and it's gonna--
-等等  有安全带吗  -凯伦
- Hold on. Do we have seat belts? - Hey, Karen.
乔伊
Joyce!
天呐  能见到你真是太好了
Oh, my gosh! How funny to see you here!
孩子们呢
Where are the kids?
我没见到他们  他们好像还没来
I... I haven't seen them. I don't think they're here yet.
-你们三个  靠墙  -不  他们在哪
- You three, up against the wall! - No, where are they?
天呐  我现在都记不住了
Oh, my gosh, I can hardly keep track these days.
他们去了...
Uh, they were at, uh...
达斯汀家  然后是卢卡斯家
Dustin's, then Lucas's,
-然后是麦克斯家  -麦克斯
- then Max's. - Max...
你知道的  夏天嘛
You know how it is. Summer!
可能又去惹什么麻烦了
Probably getting into some kinda trouble.
最后警告  你俩  靠墙
Last warning, you two. Up against the wall!
别开机
Hold the ride!
后果自负  大块头
On your life, Magnum.
开始咯
Here we go!
我的老天
Holy smokes!
老天啊
路
Roads?
我们要去的地方  不需要有路
Where we're going, we don't need roads.
好了
And...
融入
blend.
太棒了
It is so good!
-成功了  -当然
- Well, shit, that worked. - Course it worked.
我们只需要跟其他平民一起上大巴
We just have to get on the bus with the rest of these plebes,
然后就回家了
and home sweet home, here we come.
-达斯汀  -怎么了
- Uh, Dustin? - What?
我们最好别去你家
Yeah, we might not wanna go to your house.
为什么
Why?
我可能把你的全名告诉他们了
Well, I might've told them your full name.
-你什么毛病  -哥们  我被下药了
- What is wrong with you? - Dude, I was drugged.
-那又如何  -什么
- So? - So?
你抵抗啊  撑过去  像个男人那样
So, you resist. You tough it out. You tough it out like a man.
是啊  你说得轻巧
Oh, yeah, it's easy for you to say.
伙计们
Guys?
抱歉打扰  祝您晚上愉快
Sorry for the inconvenience. Have a pleasant evening.
放弃
Abort.
放弃  放弃
Abort. Abort.
该死
Shit.
好吧
Okay.
快走
Come on, let's go, let's go.
三个绿色
That's three green!
第4个飞镖
And here's dart number four!
再来一个  就能拿到大奖
One more for the big prize!
你可以的  先生
You can do it, mister!
有赢家了
We have a winner!
来吧  女士们先生们
Step right up, ladies and gentlemen!
在这里买票
Get your tickets right here!
莫里
Murray!
看啊
Look!
没被操纵
It's not rigged!
It's not rigged.
叛徒
Traitor.
阿列克西
Alexei!
不不  天呐  我们走
Oh, no. Oh, my God. Let's go.
慢点
Easy.
摁住了
Keep pressure on it.
我去找人帮忙
I'll get you help.
I'll get help.
吉姆
Jim... Jim.
Jim!
他们打伤了阿列克西  吉姆
They got Alexei, Jim!
吉姆  阿列克西
Jim! Alexei!
他们打伤了阿列克西  吉姆
They got Alexei, Jim!
我们得走了
We gotta go.
-我们得走了  -什么
- We gotta go. - What?
快走
Let's go.
他们真是奇怪的一对  是吧
They make an odd couple, don't they?
就像人说的
Well, it's like they say,
谁都能找到适合自己的人
there's someone for everyone.
谁想要热狗
Who wants a hot dog?
找到莫里  上车
Find Murray, get the car,
-开到后面来  -好
- bring it around back. - Okay.
前往"高顶"
Heading to "Big Top."
园游会东北区
Northeast side of the fair.
快上来  女士们先生们
Step right up, ladies and gentlemen!
在这里买"高顶"的票
Get your tickets to the Big Top here!
...密西西比州这边
...this side of the Mississippi.
快带孩子离开  警察
Get your kids outta here! Police!
快带他们离开
Get 'em out of here! Go!
-快走  -你  先生
- Go. - You, sir!
快来吧
Step on up!
我看到你瞄着迷宫了
I see you eyeing the maze!
别意外  别害怕
Don't be surprised! Don't be scared!
上来吧  先生
Step on up, sir!
你敢踏进恐怖洞吗
Do you dare enter the cave of horrors?
你无从知道转个角会发现什么
You never know what you might find around the corner.
别在老虎面前显露恐惧
Don't show your fear in the presence of the tiger.
否则你可能别想活着逃出去了
Or you may never escape this cave alive.
阿列克西
Alexei!
天呐
Oh, my God.
我就离开了一下
I... I just left for a minute...
去买玉米热狗
for a corn dog.
该死的玉米热狗
A stupid corn dog.
天呐
Oh, God.
不
Oh, no.
瓦西里  你在吗  瓦西里  回答
Vasilev, are you there? Vasilev? Answer!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
-拉里  -乔伊
- Larry. - Joyce.
好样的  女士
Yeah, lady!
同志
Comrade!
放开我
Get off me!
该死
Goddamn!
Son of a bitch!
快跑  走
Hit it. Hit it! Go! Go!
阿列克西呢
Alexei?
在下层
On the lower level--
翻译
Hey, translate.
我们找到孩子了
We've found the children.
他们还在商场  下层
They are still in the mall. Lower level.
封锁所有入口
Keep all entrances locked down.
重复
I repeat--
封锁所有入口
Keep all entrances locked down.
所有人  过来
Everyone, get over here.
我找到他们了
I found them.
搞什么
What the hell?
你丢那玩意就像丢风火轮一样
You flung that thing like a Hot Wheel!
-卢卡斯  -你怎么在这儿
- Lucas? - What are you doing here?
问他们啊  都怪他们
Ask them. It's their fault.
是啊  的确都怪我们
True, yeah. Totally true. It's absolutely our fault.
我不懂那车是怎么了
I don't understand what happened to that car.
一一有超能力
El has superpowers.
-什么  -超能力  她靠念力丢的车
- I'm sorry? - Superpowers. She threw it with her mind.
-跟上  -她是一一
- C'mon, catch up. - That's El?
-一一是谁  -抱歉  你是谁
- Who's El? - I'm sorry, who are you?
我是罗宾  史蒂夫的同事
I'm Robin. I work with Steve.
她破解了绝密密文
She cracked the top secret code.
我们就是这样发现了苏联人的事
Yeah, which is how we found out about the Russians in the first place.
苏联人  什么苏联人
Russians? Wait, what Russians?
-苏联人  -那是苏联人
- The Russians! - Those were Russians?
-有些是  -你说什么呢
- Some of them. - What are you talking about?
-你们没听到我们的红色警报吗  -嗯
- Didn't you hear our code red? - Yeah.
-但我根本听不懂  -该死的电池
- Couldn't understand what you were saying. - Goddamn low battery.
这事我都跟你说多少次了
How many times do I have to tell you with the low battery?
这不一切都好吗
Well, everything worked out, didn't it?
都好  我们差点死了
Worked out? We almost died.
是啊  但我们不是没死吗
Yeah, but we didn't, did we?
-挺悬的了  -好吧  苏联人
- It was pretty damn close. - Okay, Russians?
他们是在为苏联政府工作吗
As in, they're working for the Russian government?
你是哪里不理解
What are you not comprehending?
我说的不是英语吗
Am I not speaking English?
现在完全是《红色黎明》的情况
We have a full-blown Red Dawn situation.
这跟大门无关吗
So this has nothing to do with the gate?
跟大门非常有关
It has everything to do with the gate...
一一
El! El!
-她怎么了  -怎么了
- What's wrong with her? - What's wrong?
我的腿
My leg. My leg.
她的腿  好吧
Her leg, her leg. Okay.
-拿掉  -好
- Get that off. - Okay.
一一
El! El!
一一  你没事吧
El! El, are you okay?
一一
El! El!
El!